Today I am going to show you the eighth wonder of the world:
How to prepare a brownie, in five minutes, in a mug.
We need a mug,
and two spoons: a large spoon and a small spoon-
See? This is the little girl, the daughter:
Mom, Mom! Daughter!
Ingredients: flour, oil,
this is olive oil, but any oil works:
it can be coconut or sunflower oil.
But I have olive.
Water.
Salt.
Sal.
Get out of here! ...No.
And cocoa powder.
Cocoa, chocolate: powder.
This is ... this is cocoa.
In fact it is colacao, because I do not have pure cocoa.
Colacao is a brand to make chocolate milk in Spain.
It's my favorite.
We are going to take all the measures with a large spoon:
We start with the dry ingredients, that is:
The flour, the sugar, the cocoa powder and the salt.
When you take the measurements, they have to be flat, okay?
This is level: it has to be flat.
It can't be a mountain of flour.
This cannot be, this is not leveled.
Brown sugar:
Also 4 leveled tablespoons.
This is not leveled-
I've spread it everywhere ...
Now cocoa:
Two leveled tablespoons
A pinch of salt.
Salt is very important, very important.
Don't forget, you have to put a little bit of salt.
And now we mix it up.
We mix it well and once it is very well mixed,
we add the water ...
Two tablespoons.
And the oil.
Oops ... just there, just there, just there.
We mix it again.
Okay, and the texture has to be something like this.
When you have this texture,
it's ready to go into the microwave.
Depending on the power, if it is a very strong microwave, you put less time.
If it's a weaker microwave, you put it more time.
And you have to put it around 1 minute: 1 minute and 10 seconds or 50 seconds ...
That's where the time range is.
Ah! It burns, it burns, it burns, it burns!
Be careful because it burns a lot when it comes out of the microwave.
The brownie has a pretty good texture, look:
This is a recipe that I prepare when I am very hungry and I want chocolate,
but I do not have much time.
So with 5 minutes, these ingredients, and a microwave,
you can make a delicious brownie.
I leave the recipe here,
and if you also make it, tell me in a comment.
Say: Hey Laura! I made myself a brownie too!
And you tell me if you liked it or not.
If you did not like it at all.
For more Spanish, don't forget to subscribe.
And see you next week-
Bye!